All right, start dancing. That's right. Move those shoulders of yours. You know I want to see you dance. You know what I want and like by now. That's right. This is a good start. Now get ready. Attack! Hit it! Okay, act scared. Someone's after you. Okay, get ready for the next. Now you're on the hunt. You're out looking for prey.
Show me that face. Nice. Keep that smile up. I want to see you confident now. I don't want to see the slightest insecurity on your face. You hear me? But of course you would never cross me. You know what will happen.
All right, back on the dance floor. And keep up that smile. Keep dancing. Keep it going. Now arms and hands. Good. Move that booty of yours. Yeah.
Okay, now don't be scared. Okay, do a fast expand. Nice. Is that the best you've got? I don't think this is making me happy. Still not happy. You better think up something fast right now or they will suffer.
I'm not happy about this. I'm not happy. Hey, you piece of shit. Did I tell you to stop dancing? You do want to make me happy, right?
So do what I tell you and with a smile on your face. You better get back to work. Right fucking now.
For that little stunt, I think I'll break every bone in their bodies now. Yes, we made a deal. Remember, you are with me whether or not you want to be.
You'll stay here forever. You'll never be able to leave. This is your place now. This is your home.
And you will keep dancing and smiling and doing what I tell you. Does that not make you angry? Let me see some anger.
That's beautiful. Show me the anger. Yeah. Now add confused. Don't stop until I tell you. You know what will happen if you don't follow my instructions, don't you?
Okay, slowly start crying. I said slowly. That's it. And then turn it into a close up. Come in. Come in closer. You know what I like by now, don't you?
Yes, that's it. That's it. Okay. You deserve a break. You've done well today. You have pleased me greatly. You're doing so well. And you belong to me forever. Don't forget that.
Okay. That's about enough. We got to get back to work. Think about them. Okay. Think about them. Let's go. How's everybody doing?
Today is Saturday. And it's a great day because it's Saturday.
Oh, yeah. We're back in Terraria. How's everybody doing? Auto fun. Hello, Oliver. You helped my sleep with your streams, even though you scream and wake me up sometimes. Oh, I'm sorry. I can be quiet this time if you need to sleep. I'll do that for you.
I'm doing good. How about you? Magic Marquis. I'm also doing great. Yes. Lots of exciting things are happening with my life right now outside of the whole YouTube stuff. So it's a little bit overwhelming what's going on, but it's pretty cool. Yeah.
Did you guys like the intro? You guys make the funniest shit, man. I had to show it off. Scream away, dude.
Okay, but I don't scream on purpose. I scream when I get excited or scared. Auto fun punk. Auto fun punk. Punk. I don't know how to pronounce your name. I'm sorry. Hello from Australia. Hey, Phoenix. North Star. Hi, Oliver. You're my favorite YouTuber. Oh, that's cool. You're my favorite star.
It was like I was on shrooms. Nice. I like the sneak peek into the direction of the rain world feeling. I have no idea what you're talking about.
Wait, did you see something you weren't meant to see? I have to go back and look at that. That wasn't supposed to happen.
Oliver, you're my second favorite YouTuber. Yes. That's good. As long as I'm in top three, then I'm happy.
Punk is ballsack in Swedish. Well, it also isn't Danish, but it also means wallet.
Punk is a wallet in Denmark.
The fact that you saw my cursed Minecraft images and thought, hell yeah, let's go in the street. Dude, it's funny as hell.
When I saw that, I was showing it to my friend and we were both laughing our asses off.
Oliver, I love your streams. That's good. I like it.
That makes me very happy. Do you understand?
Thank you. Have a good day.
I don't get to that point where it's just spam, you know. I mean, I'm fine with people writing messages, of course.
But there's a difference between that and just spamming a bunch of stuff, right?
Finally catching you live, loved Minecraft and Terraria. Hey, Terraria is not over yet, Bernie.
Okay. This is a weekend with Bernie. 2905. Get ready.
I should create a demon man rain world skin.
You're my favorite streamer and also the only streamer I watch. That's crazy because I don't really stream that much.
It's more of a whenever I have the time and lost for it. That's not the right word in English.
The time and the inclination, I guess.
Okay. Let's get back into Terraria here, huh?
I am actually quite excited because I experienced quite some stuff last time.
Also, let me quickly close chat. Guys, I'll see you on the other side.
Hold on. There we go.
Okay. I'm flying blind.
I didn't change any audio settings since last time, so audio should be fine.
Let's go.
Once you use a live Chris and I didn't get to read the rest.
Okay. I'm back here, of course, because you're always back here.
Now, my question is, oh yeah, I have this now.
What was I doing last time?
Honestly, I have no clue what I was doing last time, but I do know that it's time to organize my inventory.
Like always at the start. Hold on.
There we go.
Angry larva charm. Let's... Oh, this is actually full.
You know what? I should put this weapons up here.
And make this one another accessory.
Oh, wait. Did I make this whole thing accessory? I did. Okay.
Put it in here for now.
Yeah. Get it in there.
This one, though, is kind of cool.
The vine is organic.
It goes in the chest for organics. And this is also material.
Boomstick. Put it in here.
I do like booms. Big bada boom.
Honey block. No, that goes in here. That's organic.
Bottles is in potions.
Man, I have so much stuff that I don't want to get rid of.
I'm a bit of a hoarder.
I'm realizing.
What do I want to do?
Let me see.
Man, I explored a lot down here. Look at this.
I kind of want to get to the edge here.
And then do all the other side as well, of course.
But there's also so much black emptiness here that I want to explore.
What to do first, though? What to do first?
One thing I know for sure. Let's leave the fishing stuff here for now.
There.
This one I'll bring. Magic mirror I will bring. Glowstick is good to have.
Scarab bombs. This one not useful because it doesn't work the way I thought it would work.
It is unfortunate.
The imp staff.
This was really good.
In fact, I will use that now.
Look at that. We now have an imp.
And I can go up here.
And get another imp.
And now I'm set.
So the imp staff. Let me also check this.
Hold on, game is a bit loud here.
There we go.
Oh yeah, I have a bunch of stuff in here.
Loot all and deposit.
Nice.
Bomb fish.
Oh yeah, I was doing a bunch of fishing.
I do want to put that in here.
Master bait, journeyman bait, life.
This one is actually kind of nuts.
This one is trash, I think.
Actually, no.
Maybe it's not.
In combat, it could save your life, I guess.
I guess I'll bring it.
My plan is to go down once again.
And do terraria things in the earth.
I'm going to be... Oh, silt!
Yes!
Let's silt it up.
I wonder if I can get something really rare doing this.
What am I getting?
Anything incredible?
Incredibly special?
I'm getting all kinds of ore out of that.
Okay, now we can click this button.
Very nice.
This one is nice.
Fleeting magi luminescence.
Moon glow goes in here.
No, actually goes up there.
But the thing is, I can't be...
Actually, I can. Hold on.
Put this here for now.
All these things that I don't immediately need.
Honestly, the campfire?
Fuck the campfire.
It's another slot to carry around.
And how often do I realistically use the best statue anyway in the Heart Lantern?
I mean, I guess they...
I almost never use this.
I'm gonna make it a thing now to keep using it.
Yeah.
Thorns.
Night owl.
Also, give me the rest here.
So I can click this button.
Art reach restoration.
I'm gonna put this in here.
Got stars coming in.
Masterful flame lash.
I kind of forgot about that.
That's also a weapon, isn't it?
Controllable ball of fire.
Let me actually try that once more.
And switch my...
Let's see here.
It's like controllable.
Similar to...
Well, the other weapon I have that is controllable.
That masterful magic missile, yeah.
Actually, it's pretty much the same weapon.
18 mana, 12 mana.
But that's because of the minus 14% mana cost.
50 magic damage.
4% crit.
But this one can set enemies a flame, right?
They're both masterful.
This one also has minus 14% mana cost, but it still costs more mana.
So I guess there's a difference there between magic missile and flame lash.
Oh yeah, they're not the same weapon, of course, because this one tracks.
Night owl, the bait. The bait can go in the chest because I'm not going fishing now.
This one is nice.
I guess this one I can also leave here.
Otherwise, I'll just fucking bring things everywhere if I don't...
You know, set a line in the sand somewhere.
And say nope, no more.
Leave it here.
Leave this also.
No, this one I'll bring.
In case I need to summon my imp.
But then again...
I've already summoned them.
And the only way they're going away is if I die.
And then I'll be back here, so...
Leave it here.
Titan potion, I don't want that.
Unless...
I should play around with it.
I haven't really tried it.
Let me try it this time.
Maybe it's sick.
This one is now empty.
Let me deposit my...
Didn't I have...
Didn't I have way more gold?
Am I crazy?
Hold on a second.
Didn't I have a shit ton of gold?
I had a platinum.
Or the...
Whatever this one is.
The grey one.
I had that.
What the fuck?
Did I spend it?
I must have spent it on something.
Where did I buy?
Or maybe I died.
Maybe I actually died and lost it all somewhere.
Where did I die last?
Oh, I was in the jungle?
It doesn't actually show the X.
That's interesting.
Okay.
Well...
Potions, put this in here.
Mining potion is definitely a...
Great one to have.
This one as well.
Potion of Return is super great to have as well.
Look at all these potions.
I will put them in here.
Because it's one of those times where I just need to drink it once.
And then it's done.
Also this.
This goes here.
This one goes...
Let's say...
Is there anything here I don't use?
This is like my...
baseline setup here.
Oh, I have two axes.
Maybe I don't need two.
That's a bit overkill.
Let's put this in here.
Even though this one is technically better for some...
horse.
Whatever.
We're gonna put the Ham axe here.
And because this is an axe...
I don't need this.
So this one I can also put in here.
The Bognet...
I never really use it.
Let's also put it in here for now.
Maybe at some point I will need it, but not right now.
There we go. Look at this.
This has to be my standard...
setup.
Maybe I'll even remove the dirt, and instead...
always have wooden platforms instead.
Because they're actually better all the time.
Anyway.
Do I have more wooden pl-
I should just make a bunch.
Just make a shit ton of these wooden platforms.
It's good to have.
And then the wood I can put in here.
There we go.
Look at how I cleaned up this inventory.
This...
This is peak.
Okay?
Peak performance right now.
If I want to do it even better.
I'm gonna put the magic mirror here as well.
And you may think, why? Don't you need that?
I don't, actually.
Because I get so many of these potions anyway.
And they stack up, right?
Recall.
So this will actually free up an inventory slot for me.
And these are faster anyway.
Right?
And there it is.
Torches.
I'm going bare minimum here.
Okay.
And that's it.
I think I'm ready.
Also, what goes in here?
This is money.
How's my outfit?
I have the spectra boots, obsidian shield.
The horseshoe balloon.
Quickly summon this.
Where's that replacement...
Oh, that's what I need to bring.
That's what I need to bring.
I need to bring either this...
or what was the other one I usually use there?
Violent bone glove, maybe.
Maybe I should try something new.
Let's just see here.
Automatically use mana potions when needed.
This 8% reduced mana cost is actually kind of nice.
I do like that.
I also have this, but that's so annoying to have equipped.
I'm not going to equip that.
Immunity to knockback.
Oh, I already have that.
Immunity to curse.
Curses when I can't use my items.
Slowly regenerates life.
No, I don't want that.
I think my best option is actually either the Violent Bone Glove.
Or...
the Magi Illuminescence thing.
Oh, and that is here.
This one is super good, man.
Provides light when... yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is... I mean, not right now, but leave it here.
Because this is the one I need to exchange quickly.
Okay.
Nice. We are ready to go explore.
And you know what else?
While I'm exploring,
I will actually prioritize items.
I will choose not to pick up certain items.
Unless I'm absolutely sure that I need to use them later.
I guess I want to go straight down here and then go left now.
Or I could also go back to the jungle.
But then again, also want to check out the ice.
What's below the ice here?
Also, this looks interesting. This whole area there.
Didn't get to explore much of that. There's more over here.
Oh, yeah, let's go west.
Go west.
What's up, squirrel?
It's adventure time.
So for now, I'll put this on because it makes me fast.
Look at the speed right here. Whoops.
Oh my God, I can't hit anything.
I gotta remember to play this game.
Or how to play it.
Man, it actually does feel good to be back in Terraria.
I just don't know how to say it. Terraria or Terraria?
I guess if it's actually meant to be a Terrarium,
another one you put animals in, I guess it's Terraria then.
But if it's meant as Earth, like Terra, then it's Terrarium, right?
Actually, I'm not sure.
Whatever.
I guess it's actually meant as a Terrarium.
Because there's an item in here that's such a Terrarium.
It's very fitting.
Oh wait, didn't we also... there was a meteor that came down.
I wonder why that came down.
I remember this.
There was a meteor somewhere. Also, where am I going?
I want to go down here again.
So let me go... wait.
Wait, there is a desert!
Did I just completely gaslight myself into thinking there was no desert last time?
I just think you remember thinking...
I thought there was a desert. How silly of me.
Are you kidding right now?
Open this.
I want to drink this.
I want to equip that because we're going mining, boys.
Do that.
I'm going to go straight down here.
Let's do another one of those straight downs.
I don't know why. This is so much fun to just go straight down.
We need party lights. That's on this key bind.
Let's try not to die this time.
Catch your breath. Nice.
Look how fast we're mining.
Come on. Get me to a cave.
I need to make an emergency thingy here.
Air. Nice.
And then...
Oh, and here we are.
I'm so powerful right now. I have my imps with me.
I'm actually taking straight down into a cave I've already been in.
That's fun.
Uh oh.
Oh, I'm gonna die.
I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
That was a bit too close.
By the way, today is the day where I won't die a single time.
I know it sounds hard to believe,
but this today is actually that day.
I've just been kidding all these other times.
This is the real deal.
Okay. No, no, go straight down.
Keep going down. Keep going down. What are you doing, dude?
So I was here. Keep going down.
Oh, no.
Okay.
We're good.
All right. Take a swig.
Nice.
Uh oh, uh oh.
Something is damaging me.
Let me see. Where did I dig?
I'm in the center now, so straight down.
I love doing these verticals.
Get into a cave.
There's a cave on the left.
Oh, we're breaking into this part now.
We got an emergency do this now.
I should take a potion that gives me breath, actually.
Breathing water would be the ideal thing to do here.
Snipe.
Had a glow stick in him.
Do I want to keep going down?
Or do I want to explore this a little bit more?
Is this an interesting biome?
You know what? Let's keep the digging on hold for a bit
and just explore this for a while.
Glow sticks are nice.
Blink root? Very nice.
Man, what is actually in this area?
It seems kind of empty.
Doesn't it?
Hey.
Red husk.
What is up here?
Oh, here we go. Bring it on.
Nothing.
I'm so powerful, dude.
Wait, what is this? Look how this looks.
Marble!
Hello! Oh, look at this!
That's cool.
Let's see.
Okay.
I haven't heard about the marble.
Violent depth meter.
Another one. That's the second violent depth meter I have.
Why are the depth meters so violent in this game?
So odd.
So what can I actually get from this biome?
Oh, what's that?
A bone sword.
Alright.
It's not a material, unfortunately.
But I'll try it nonetheless.
It's a sword.
It does sword things.
Okay, I kind of want to...
So look at the map here.
Look at that, how that looks.
That's interesting.
Also the marble stuff?
Marble block.
It's a material.
It's not that interesting of a material.
Let's go down.
Dark here.
Okay, now we're out of that biome.
Okay, that was weird.
Hold on.
What did I learn about the marble biome?
Someone in town told me about it.
There's nothing in there either.
Hoplight.
Javelin.
Cool.
Not bad.
I kind of want to check out the rest of the marble stuff.
There's got to be more in here.
Oops.
What?
Die.
Where could it be?
Oh, that's a lot of damage.
He dropped another sword.
Or javelin I guess.
So there's nothing up there.
Nothing down here.
This is a very small biome.
Weird.
Okay.
I like it though.
There's a variety there.
Okay, I'm going to continue my journey downwards over here.
It's time.
Where did that?
Dude, I'm so freaking powerful.
Feels good.
Not that way.
Where did I hear?
I fell from here, so I just go like that.
Man, it's so quick.
The glow stick is actually fantastic.
Especially because it comes with you when you dig.
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
Straight.
Here I've been before.
I don't even care. I'm still going straight down.
I'm keeping a close eye on my breath this time.
I don't want to accidentally drown again.
I've had enough of that.
There's just so much water here.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
Drain that water.
Oh, look at that down there.
Crimp-tane.
That is crimp-tane, isn't it?
It is. It sure is.
Give me that breath.
Keep going down.
I'm actually so excited to see where we emerge down below.
Like, maybe it'll be different here to the west.
Finally, we get to drain a little bit here.
Drain all the water.
Keep going down.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
Great statue.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la.
Oh, we've got a hub light.
Drops more javelins, it seems.
Keep going down.
I think my potion wore off. Look how slow I am.
But wait, is this also a marble?
Another marble biome.
Let's explore this one.
Bombs, nice.
Also, my inventory is getting a little full here.
So, what I'm going to do here, like that, put that there.
Switch back.
Okay, what do we have?
Maybe these biomes are just that small.
Just very small biome.
Oops.
Okay.
I'm getting a lot of marble.
Probably looks nice when making things.
I mean, marble is a pretty nice material, isn't it?
Oh, this is a bit bigger.
Life crystal?
Alright.
I'm scared of hazards.
That's actually a cave right below me, it seems. Hold on.
Hold on.
I want to see this.
I'm so dark.
Okay, we're fine.
Oh my god, they're mine.
I was like, hold on.
The imps are on my side.
God damn it.
Keep forgetting.
Sometimes it's hard to tell, man.
In the middle of combat, you're like, I don't know.
Okay, I don't want to go down here, actually.
I want to keep my plan going.
My digging plan.
Black slime banner?
Let's put that here.
Why not?
That's what I say.
We're still wearing the thing, yeah.
Marble is just hard to get through, man. This is tough.
Cheers, everybody. Happy Saturday.
Here we go, stone.
He dealt a lot of damage to me just now.
There's some lights in here.
Pop light on the right.
That's all right.
Man, how far down am I?
Oh, I'm not even that far down.
I thought it was way down.
Oh, here we go.
Starting to look like something.
I think it's time to consume a certain potion.
Also, deposit everything.
Delete stuff I don't want.
I guess these.
The bone sword? I don't want that.
Heart and sand can also go away.
Clay can go away.
Cobwebs go away.
This one.
Tin.
Mud.
Uh, vertebra.
I guess these ones, too, are taking up a lot of room for no reason.
Dirt.
Stone.
Sand.
Silt I want to keep.
Marble.
I want to keep that, actually.
Let me see what that's all about.
Okay, nice.
Clean inventory.
And then we need to drink a potion.
Obsidian skin.
Do it.
And also...
Mining speed.
Go!
Mega speed.
If not for these potions here...
It would have been so terrible getting down here.
Having to avoid all the lava.
There we go.
Should be there soon.
Man, my finger hurts from holding the button.
I need to use my other finger for this.
Oh, railway!
Hey!
I don't even care about him.
My minions take care of it.
Look at that.
I'm just here to dig.
I don't care about anything.
My bodyguards are with me.
Okay, we're approaching.
Look at the background.
Killed that guy as well.
Here we are.
Actually, I will take these.
I don't know why I'm collecting all this.
They just seem rare, you know?
You don't see them that much.
We have done it.
Okay, we're fine, actually.
Okay.
Where are we?
Let me keep going left.
No, let me go right and connect everything.
That's the plan.
And let's start looting.
My favorite part.
That's a hellforge.
Ooh, nice painting there.
Lake of fire.
I want that as well.
Flowing magma.
Okay.
Keep going right.
We got to get the gold back, man.
I don't know where the fuck my gold went.
I had so much gold on me.
It was actually wild.
Speaking of gold, I should regularly put this in my...
my trough.
You know what? It's easier to just take through here.
I'm taking some damage here.
This guy's annoying. I can't get to him.
Okay, he's down here.
He's up there now.
Come on, minions. Take care of him.
Oh, that's a decorative thing.
I'm going in here.
Don't care about anything.
What's that?
Thorns. Oh, I'll take it.
In fact, let me also put this on.
Autopause goes back on.
Gimme.
Nice.
And return! Hey!
That's a fantastic potion.
One of my favorites.
Oh.
What's going on there?
Oh, I didn't bring my...
Oh, no.
Okay, this is why we have this potion.
Potion of Return. We need to use it right now.
Plop!
I didn't bring my key.
The key is essential.
Where did I put the key?
In keys, probably.
Yeah.
And then we can also quickly empty our shit.
Put this in here.
This one.
Can I do the...
Oh, I can't lock them in here.
So when I take things, they stay.
That's annoying.
It's okay, though.
Gold. All this.
Besser life crystal.
Nice.
And now, there.
Marble.
Quickly.
Dylan!
What do you think about this marble that I found?
Is that special?
I can polish it and make it smooth.
Why would I polish it?
I don't understand.
Nope, put this in here.
And the silt! It's silt time.
Dude, I love silt.
Oh wait, I have to do this.
Cool.
And then...
The last thing is to click this button.
And now we're back.
Key!
There.
Lock it, please.
There we go.
Nice.
No.
No, no, no.
Go back.
We go back.
A strong sun fury.
It's the same amount of damage.
Less critical strike.
More knockback.
It's bad.
But I'll take it anyway.
I'll take this as well.
This one I can delete.
That one.
Teleportation.
Random location!
I definitely want to do that.
Let's drink the invisibility potion.
Because why not?
It's cool to be invisible.
Let's go silent through these areas.
A godly dark lands.
What the fuck does godly mean?
Dynamite.
I'll take it.
Oh yes!
Gravitation nice.
Oh yeah, baby.
I love looting in this game.
There's just potions hanging out here.
Another return potion.
That's so big.
Hey you!
Another voodoo demon.
What is it with that voodoo thing?
I don't understand.
A hell wing bow.
Wouldn't arrows turn into flaming bats?
Wait, what?
Hold on.
What are you saying?
I need to test this immediately.
Oh shit, I'm dying here.
Oh wait, I think I need to...
Oh!
Oops.
So this is a track?
Or how does that work?
I mean, they're definitely flaming bats.
Hmm, not very much damage though.
I don't like it.
Maybe I'll like it later.
I don't like it now.
City and brick.
I don't want that.
Let's get some more chests.
Platinum.
Dynamite.
Oh!
Increases enemy spawn rate.
Oh yeah, I don't want that.
That's not something I want to activate.
Or maybe I do at some point.
Let's heal up a bit here.
Let's just chillax.
Actually, sometimes it's annoying that a game...
I wish there was a key pine to just turn this off and on.
Actually, maybe there is...
Autopause?
Because it's something that I want to switch between all the time.
Maybe not.
Just so I can organize my inventory while I wait for this to heal.
Somehow the dynamite doesn't automatically stack.
That's weird.
Put the money in, by the way.
All these potions.
I guess these things I can sell.
Oh!
This one!
Gotcha.
Heal up.
What are you shooting at?
Oh, I see, I see.
Also, I forget I have this weapon.
The hundredth Hellbat!
Very nice.
I cannot regret not bringing my campfire now.
What's that?
Hold on.
Do I still have that effect on me?
Ooh, I don't.
Cascade.
Can I quickly grab it without dying, I wonder?
Probably not.
I am gonna...
quickly use another obsidian potion.
Ha!
Thank you.
Let's see what it is.
Average knockback is another yo-yo.
Is it actually good or not?
I mean...
Not really.
I'm not impressed, you know?
Hop!
Dynamite everywhere.
Instead of deleting it, it's more fun to let it just blow something up, isn't it?
Okay, let's grab this lantern now.
Okay.
Let's keep moving.
We have lava protection, so don't be afraid.
So nice that these things drop healing potions, actually.
I don't have to craft them myself.
Ooh, what's shooting?
Okay, health fire arrow.
More fire blossoms?
That's good, because I can use those to make obsidian potions.
Ooh, that's a big one.
That's a nice painting.
Shining moon.
What's this?
Obsidian bed.
You know what? I have an idea.
Can I actually use this?
Is time going down here?
Faster?
2pm?
Wait, what?
Wait, so 2pm?
I'm sleeping now.
It's not working.
Unfortunately.
Goddammit.
Hey, what's up, dude?
Be kind of cool if you could fast forward through the night.
Hey.
Ooh, what's that?
Oh, invisibility.
I guess I'll use it.
Also, why does this...
Oh, man.
I wish it would keep being locked after I pick it up again.
Ash can go away.
Let's drink that.
Let's go.
Oh, it's actually kind of hard to see where I am now,
but I guess I have obsidian on me, so it's fine.
Oh.
Healing potion.
Oh, you.
Thank you.
You there.
Stop existing.
Are you shooting me?
Oh, down here.
It's so dark, I need to put out some lights here.
Another screen poster and a piano.
Yeah.
Hey, you there.
Another one of these.
Come here.
What's happening?
What the fuck is that?
Uh-oh.
What's happening?
Shoot it.
What the fuck?
I'm running.
Oh, my God.
Move.
Just fucking kill it, whatever it is.
Holy shit.
It's following me.
I need to heal.
Some kind of boss.
Wait, I've been here.
Oh, you know what?
Real quick.
Auto pause on, just so I can collect my thoughts right now.
Potato chips.
Eat it.
Money trough.
Ah.
What do I need?
Thorns.
Let's use life force.
Yes.
And...
Yes, because I don't know how long it's left on my other one.
I don't...
Man of Regen-
Sure.
Night owl.
Okay.
That one.
We gotta go, we gotta go.
Okay, and then.
Nice.
And then.
Bro, I have no idea what's going on.
I gotta heal.
Okay, potion is used.
Kill it.
Okay, shoot these fucking tentacle things.
Okay, it's not that bad actually.
But what happens when I run out of space?
We still have a long way to go though, no?
Dig!
Oh, shit.
What the fuck is that now?
I'm learning low on HP here.
Holy shit.
Come on minions, help me!
Oh, I'm kinda stuck here.
Oh!
What the fuck's happening?
Holy shit!
Oh my god.
What the fuck?
Okay, I angered someone down there.
Alright.
Damn.
Oh.
Well, well, well.
I was actually wondering whether or not there would be a boss down there.
Seems like there is a boss.
Dude, I am shaking man.
That was something.
I gotta go back there immediately and kill it.
Put this in here.
Fix the inventory.
Also bring potions now.
What do I want?
I want...
Uh...
I don't know.
Calming?
Wouldn't be too bad, I guess.
Bring that.
Sonar.
Wormhole.
Featherfall.
Man, I need to calm down.
Let me hang this somewhere.
Okay, okay.
Oh!
Man.
Yup.
Oh, I should have had this on for fuck's sake.
Run... actually running faster there?
Would that have helped me?
I'm flying most of the time.
What can I use?
Probably this one is great.
Nope, not there.
There.
Damn.
Damn, damn, damn.
That just scared me.
Put this here.
Put this.
Put stuff in here.
Stuff I want to sell.
You.
Buy my helwing bow.
This one...
I will keep, because I want to try that, actually.
Yeah, let me keep that for now.
No.
I'm going to put that in my weapons chest.
This one I already have, so you can have that.
You can have that.
Switch outfit, please.
And then...
Michelinius.
Where did I put this guy before?
Okay, so what the fuck did I just die to?
Wall of flesh has awoken.
Wait.
Dylan was slain.
Connor has arrived.
No!
What happened?
Dylan!
Why did you die?
And it happened right at the same time, by the way.
Wait a minute.
Was the wall of flesh awoken because Dylan died?
Oh wait, I can't kill him.
What the...
I am so confused by what is happening right now.
But you know what?
Let's make some potions.
Because I need to make insane potions now.
Dylan, remind me what I need.
Oh, I mean, Connor!
Fuck!
Dylan is gone!
Dylan!
Whoops.
Okay, what do I need against that shit?
Ah, let's see here.
Mana regeneration.
Would be nice.
So, you know what? Let me...
Okay, so I need Moon Glow, Daybloom.
Lead?
A lot of Daybloom, actually.
Okay.
And then I also need...
I want...
Is this...
Is this magic damage?
So you definitely want this...
Deathweed and Moon Glow.
Man, how much Moon Glow do I have?
Moon Glow, I have seven.
That's not a lot.
I need that.
Let me actually just take these.
Here?
What do I have in here?
Daybloom?
Oh, I don't have a lot of that either!
Holy shit!
Wait, mushroom?
I don't...
Hmm.
Give me this.
Make me...
I need lead.
Lead, lead, lead.
I know, I need lead ore.
Or iron ore.
Lead ore.
I have more lead than iron.
Yes.
Make five of these, man.
I wonder...
What kind of damage I took there?
I guess physical.
Right, so this is a good potion.
Okay.
Is there anything else I want to make?
Let's see here.
Connor?
I need to see about making more.
Okay.
Shine potion.
It's actually shining!
Look at that!
Night owl potion.
Battle thorns.
Maybe this?
I have it already, actually.
Yeah, maybe I'll use that.
Oh, maybe I did use it last time.
I forgot.
Fishing, crate, Titan.
Dangerous and sonar flipper.
Oh!
This one!
Oh, I don't have a variegated lard to fish.
Crap.
Oh well.
Inferno.
Criticals.
This could be nice.
I don't have a hemo piranha.
Wrath.
Ebon koi.
Don't have it.
Oh, I guess you get this from this region where the death weed is.
Like ebon is like something dark, right?
Specular fish.
Throw this to make someone fall in love.
Wait.
Luck.
What does this even mean, luck?
Maybe it's just in general when you kill enemies.
What is the chance of getting something nice?
That's what I think that is.
Biome sight potion.
Flask of poison.
Flask of fire.
What? Mealy and whip attacks make enemies drop more gold?
Whip attacks.
I don't think I've seen a whip.
Why is it only...
Oh yeah, by the way, I was told it's called melee.
So I've been saying this word wrong for a while.
I'm gonna try and see if I remember this now.
Flask of party.
Okay, I think my potion game is strong right now.
Let's go in here.
And whoop, not that.
Deposit these again.
Potion game is strong.
And then in here.
And there.
And we're ready.
This one can also go in here for now.
Oh, there's no more room.
Sell this one.
To you.
Wait.
No, what?
Fucking... I don't know.
Sell this one, please.
Here.
Now, this...
Okay, this looks good.
Although, did I drop some gold just now?
Where did I die?
Oh, wait, it shows me...
Wait, what?
Has it always done this?
Usually says an X.
What the heck?
I don't think I remember this.
At all.
So, what the fuck did I do down there to...
trigger this shit?
Maybe I delved too deep.
Okay, let's keep going.
I want to go back down there, man.
That looked very...
Oh.
Look at this.
Does that mean I'm now immune to...
Oh, provide sevens.
Oh, okay, so it's just in the beginning.
I see.
Okay, get off now.
Whoa.
But look at this now.
Look how far we're gonna fall.
Oh, yeah.
Isn't this satisfying?
Would I just pick up?
Whoopsie.
I picked up something just now.
Okay, man.
I gotta be ready for this now.
What did I do last time?
Oh, I forgot to summon my thingies.
God, crappy damage.
Superior rally.
That's what I just got.
Drink this, please.
Man.
I have no idea how that just happened before.
Maybe I broke something.
Like, I broke for the other ones that spawned, you know?
Like, I had to break those parts or whatever.
Maybe without knowing it, I did something.
But honestly, I have no idea what I did.
And I've been here.
So I went this way.
Let's see where I went to.
What's the last point is?
Is this where I...
No, this is not where I died, is it?
Why died there?
These chests have already looted.
So I went over here.
Also, really quickly.
Oh, I don't have any obsidian potions left.
That's bad.
That's real bad.
Okay.
Oh, this is actually...
Oh, what am I doing?
I'm dying now.
Oh, it's so weird.
I'm not immune to it.
How the fuck am I gonna...
I guess I'll do it this way.
Okay, okay, okay.
We can do this.
I've been here.
Was it there?
I must have broken something over here.
Oh, no.
Okay, okay.
No, I remember this.
Here we go.
Demonic Flame Lash.
Another one.
Another treasure magnet.
18 restoration potions.
That's kind of a lot, isn't it?
I mean, restoration...
Let's put that first.
Such that it will get used.
First.
Let's put it there.
And at the last spot, let's put...
Sure.
Let's try this, actually.
Hey, you there.
Alright, it doesn't track.
Wait, does it?
Oh, it does track!
Oh, okay.
Okay.
It is a tracker.
I don't wanna go this way.
There's nothing here.
I'm gonna go left again.
Maybe it's something like...
Whenever you kill a certain amount of enemies,
then this happens.
It could also be a thing.
But I mean, I feel like last time I was here,
I killed a lot more.
So maybe that's not it.
Oh, how am I gonna...
Up!
There.
Come on.
What do I have on right now?
The Violent Bungla.
Okay, that's fine, actually.
That's fine.
I do like that one.
What's this?
Last hopes of man.
Alright, sure.
I feel like ever since I've discovered this one,
this one is nice,
but it's just so imprecise because during combat,
when you can't think to aim,
you're busy with other things,
it's incredibly difficult to aim precisely with it.
I have been here.
Let's keep going west.
So while it's nice and all,
it's only really good against big targets
that I can reliably hit without looking too much.
You know what I mean?
So the boss definitely had like appendages
that you could hit and destroy.
Tentacle thingies.
I think the trick is to destroy those first.
And then it's like one of those,
you've got to keep running from it.
Otherwise you die when you get...
Oh, here.
Come here.
These don't kill me.
Okay, we're fine.
Whoop.
What have we got down here?
Nothing.
Okay.
Oh, that was close.
Damn, getting lots of money here.
What did I get?
Actually delete this.
I have that already.
Oh, that's scary.
Chest.
Another flame lash.
Teleportation.
I love this potion so much.
I'm definitely going to be using those today.
Thank you.
Then we have this guy.
What is that green thing?
But it's my turtle.
Keen dark lands.
Meteorite bars.
Nice.
Life force.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Pretty cool.
Wall of flesh.
What a name.
I did go down there.
Okay.
Keep going up.
Oh, here we go.
Come on.
There it is.
I'm free of your shenanigans.
What the...
That was a geyser.
Mack my geyser.
Wait, spelunker?
What is that again?
Yeah, let's do it.
Maybe something will stand out down here that I haven't noticed yet.
I didn't know what's treasure, you know.
Let me also open this.
Deposit all my money so I don't forget.
I need to find more obsidian potions.
I feel like if that boss is coming again, I kind of need that.
Otherwise I am dead.
Oh, wait.
I don't have the thing on right now.
I am an idiot.
And all the loot.
Obsidian, come on.
In the potion.
I kind of hope the boss doesn't spawn right now.
When I need those potions first.
It's very important.
I guess I could have made them myself but I kind of forgot about it.
Do have a potion of return though.
I wonder what happens if I use that after the boss arrives.
Love these chests.
A mythical flower of fire.
Holy shit, look at how many stuff there is on that.
Throws balls of fire.
All kinds of stuff.
Let me try that.
Treasure magnet, heart reach, potion of return, nice.
And four gold, that's a lot.
Okay, so it sort of bounces.
In an arc as well.
Okay.
Featherfall, not quite what I need.
But it's okay.
Dude, this house is big.
Treasure here.
What did I get?
I got all kinds of things.
Kind of funny that I can kill these things with fire.
Even though there's fire like enemies.
Like what?
Okay, and that was that house.
And we have soon cleaned this entire place.
Oh god, careful with that.
Potion of return.
Wait, what is that up there?
Oh, tungsten.
Just randomly hanging out here.
Okay.
Let's see.
Sun fury.
More restorations, relunkers, thorns, return.
Very nice.
I mean, all of this is incredible loot.
Please, give me more of it.
Okay.
We got a big area here. We need to traverse.
Let's do it in steps.
Oh!
That was kind of a cool move I just did there.
I sort of let go right after it hits.
You don't have to let it drag you all the way up.
The hook that is.
Man, I'm scared of this boss.
Just randomly appearing.
Maybe I should just go back real quick.
Do I not have any obsidian potions?
I don't.
Not even in here?
Hold on.
It's like purple.
No, it's not there.
Put money in.
I think I may have to go back real quick.
Just in case. I got a plate safe.
Let's do it.
Return.
There we go.
Let's make some obsidian potions.
Oh, did I use all my obsidian ore?
I can't believe I've done this.
That's horrible.
It's gonna be sold.
Here, have that.
Have that as well.
And this one.
This one as well because I have one already.
Man, this one is kind of crazy.
This is a lot of damage. Holy crap.
Demonic flame lash.
Is it a material at least?
It's not.
Sell this one.
And now I have so much money again.
Whoops.
So put it in again.
And then I also want to...
Oh, I have another one of these.
I guess I sell it, huh?
Potions.
Okay, so what does it take?
To make...
Man, I need the obsidian though.
Fuck.
I'm just gonna go back, I guess.
And hope I get one.
It did drop kind of frequently before.
Didn't it?
Oh, look at that chest just hanging out there.
That's suspicious.
A ruthless flower of fire.
This one costs 11 mana.
12 mana.
And more meteorite.
Obsidian!
Hey!
Okay, nice.
It paid off.
Unpleasant flame lash.
Two more obsidian.
Oh my god.
If I just kept going, huh?
Instead of going back just now.
Oh no.
Oh!
Come here.
Oh fuck, here we go.
Okay.
It is related to that.
It's related to the demon.
Did you see the chat?
Pause!
I'm in panic mode.
Okay, okay.
Wait.
Potion time.
This one.
What's this?
Life force.
And thorns.
Oh my god, I can't do this right now.
This one.
Obsidian, of course.
Okay, and then...
What's next?
Mana regeneration?
Oh no, I forgot my...
I forgot my guys.
Oh no.
Up, up!
Oh my god.
Oh no.
Oh, this is bad.
Oh, there's big eyes on it as well, actually.
Oh my, I'm taking a lot of damage here.
Run, run, run!
Oh, keep going!
Run, run, run, run, run!
I'm stuck!
Keep focusing.
Okay, okay, okay.
Not so bad, it's actually going pretty well.
Oh, oh no.
Get up.
I just sort of accelerated somehow there.
Oh my god, here we go.
I kind of want to try this.
Oh fuck.
Is it getting faster?
Oh no.
Oh, I'm dead, I think.
Okay.
I know what happened.
It's the fucking doll.
So the demon is carrying the doll.
Look at this.
Con of the guide was slain.
It's the doll.
So wait a minute.
Wait, what?
What?
What am I looking for?
Here.
No, where did I put it?
Guide voodoo doll.
Let me bring both of these.
Uh...
Okay.
Oh, that's why I couldn't use this weapon.
I was trying to use it in the fight.
I kept pressing my key bind and nothing happened.
I didn't have it equipped.
Fuck.
No, don't do that, don't do that.
Take these back.
I want to try this.
So here's the thing.
I killed the demon with the voodoo doll.
It fell in the lava.
The doll died.
And it's a voodoo doll.
So Dylan died.
Or in this case, Connor died.
And that spawned the wall of flesh.
But why do I also have a doll of Edmund?
That's the question here.
Why do I have a doll of...
And why is this even a thing to begin with?
Why are they carrying around dolls of the guide?
Of all things.
Think about it.
Isn't that really weird?
Like, does the guide have dark ties or something to the underworld or whatever?
Shit.
Put this in here.
It makes you easier.
12% speed.
Very fast speed.
Critical strike.
4%.
Not... ooh.
And less mana cost.
You know what?
I think this is better.
Yeah.
I do.
I do think it's better.
This is now the other weapon chest right here.
Because we don't have any more room.
Fuck it.
Where'd it go?
Ah, there it is.
This goes in here.
Okay, so let's think about this.
So that fight, we have to keep running.
While we...
And by the way, next time I'm gonna bring my imps.
Which is where exactly is it?
Put it in here.
Wait, did I leave it behind?
I guess I did, right?
Imp staff.
I wonder...
Excuse me, sir.
Would you like to...
Fjäll, reforge this for me.
Wait, hello?
Hey, an unpleasant one.
I'll take it.
Unpleasant imp staff.
Ideally, I also want to make the potion that gives me one more of them.
But I don't think I can because I don't have the materials for that, unfortunately.
There we go.
Yeah, two is max right now.
Put it there.
Something tells me fire is not gonna be very effective against the guy down in the lava.
But then again, the enemies do take fire damage even though it looks like they will not take fire damage.
So what the fuck?
This one can be sold.
There you go.
My potions look pretty good, I think.
These are good.
Put this here.
Spelunker.
This one stays here because it will prioritize that.
Now the question is how do I regen HP during that?
I mean, I could just not take damage, I guess.
You know?
I mean, it sounds dumb to say it like that, but...
Maybe that's how you got to do it.
Sack!
Sack.
Who told me about this, by the way, with the thing?
There was something... someone told me something about a doll.
Wasn't there? Was it Fjellor? Someone?
Dante, actually. Hold on. Was it you?
Why can't I open this door?
Oh, it's the painting. Oh, I'm so sorry, dude.
I heard there is a doll that looks very similar to Sack somewhere in the underworld.
I'd like to put a few rounds in it.
I remember this.
Put a few rounds in it, huh?
That's very nice.
Put that there.
Okay.
Well, let's try that one more time, huh?
It's so far down, though.
Hmm.
I died there. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I had too gold on me. Maybe this has always been here. I just never noticed.
Yeah.
I just never noticed that because the X blocks it off when you zoom out like this.
Not very obvious.
Okay.
Man, I'm kind of scared of that enemy.
I don't know, dude. I feel like I should maybe get...
the magic damage potion at least.
What did that require anyway?
Magic...
Wait, wait. Yeah, this stays here.
Nope. Give me water, this one.
I guess, Sack, I'll talk to you.
Let me also deactivate this.
No, deactivate it. Oh, it was off. Okay, okay, good.
Tell me about this, Sack.
Let's see here. Magic was...
Which one was the magic?
Magic power.
Deathweed and... wait, I can make this.
Oh, I needed the phone star. Oh, shit. Okay, I could have made it.
Amazing.
And Papyr, Deathweed, Moonglow. That's it.
Let's make a bunch.
Magic power. One, two, three, four.
Let's keep some of the Moonglow for now.
This one goes here.
Okay, so here's what I think I'm gonna do.
I am manually gonna drop this doll into the lava.
Because that's where I killed the guy.
It fell into the lava.
And I'm gonna prepare before that.
Before that happens.
I'm actually gonna buff myself up completely.
I'm going back to the same job I made over here.
That's a lie, by the way, because that was my minion doing that.
That is not true.
I did not kill my 300th blue slime.
I guess I could also put rounds in it.
With a gun, maybe.
But the thing is you can't place the item in the world.
You can only throw it.
I tried that once.
No, left.
Take a sip of coffee.
I guess I got my ass handed to me.
I kind of thought I was invincible at this point.
Not quite.
Next time I got it.
Oh, wait, I passed it.
Okay, I think I should be using my hook some more.
Because it's actually an incredible tool.
You know what, actually?
Maybe it is better to have...
Where is it?
Oh man, I don't have it on me. Shit.
I was going to say it's better to have the speed one on me.
Because I'm doing a lot of running, you know?
So getting that acceleration...
Oh no.
That was a mistake.
40 seconds on fire.
Yeah, yeah, that's fine.
That's fine.
So hold on, this one?
Yeah, so this one I don't think is that great in this fight.
I need something that tracks.
AKA this one.
My problem is though, that it's costing a lot of...
mana to use this.
So I wonder if there is an armor set that is better for me in this case.
Just die.
Delete this.
You know what?
Where's my...
Oh my god, that's annoying.
Give me the up-return.
Quick to do that.
Before we start this...
I want to...
What do I want to do again? I forgot.
What did I just think about? Fuck.
It was not a potion.
Right, weapon?
Was it this one?
Oh yeah, right, also the accessory.
This one.
I want this.
Acceleration.
And... oh, this one.
Ooh, wait a minute.
No, I think this one is pretty nice. This one is like... amazing.
Maybe I don't need this. Maybe this is better because...
Damage.
Actually, I'm bringing this anyway.
That's... this one is definitely...
So, I'm going to knock...
What is fire block?
Maybe I don't need this at all.
I can put this here.
And instead of...
No, that's good, that's good.
Where's that other weapon I had?
Let's actually take a look at the weapons here.
The Star Cannon.
It's not even that much damage anymore.
This seemed insane to me when I got it, 60 damage.
But it's not actually that good.
This one, though.
Demonic Snowball Cannon?
I also have these.
Maybe this is... good.
I'm going to try that instead.
Um...
I think we are...
Man, there was something else I wanted to do here.
Why did I go back?
I went back because I...
needed to do what exactly.
Oh yeah, right.
Food also.
Media... yeah.
Bring lasagna.
We need lasagna.
Yeah.
And there's nothing else here I would like to use.
Oh wait, wasn't there...
something about walking on lava?
That would be pretty sick.
Hold on, this actually...
Is that better?
Unpredictable healing, 70?
But brief periods of inexplicable invulnerability sounds insane.
Let's do that.
And what else?
I think we're good.
That's it.
That's it!
This one.
Oh, it uses mana, actually.
So maybe that's not really what I want.
This also uses mana, I guess.
Let's go...
I guess I could also...
I mean...
I could do this.
But I feel like is this too tryhard, man?
You know, this is way too much.
There's no way I'm doing all that.
Let's do this one.
This one.
Thorns.
Max life.
Defense.
And...
Let's hang this here, I guess.
Maybe we're probably gonna run out of range anyway, so...
Does it really matter, you know?
Let me try this.
Wait, maybe that's not what I have to do.
Oh, yeah, it is.
It is.
Here we go.
Oh, zoom out, by the way, so I can see shit.
I drank a mana potion just now.
Oh no, don't fall down there.
It's actually kind of hard for me to play like this.
Oh no.
Does the game pause while I'm...
No, it doesn't, it doesn't.
I need to zoom in just a bit more, otherwise I can't really tell.
What the fuck is happening?
I guess I gotta keep moving.
I gotta keep moving.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Just go really far.
Oh, don't fall down, don't fall down.
That's bad.
Okay, maybe I should zoom out just a bit.
Where is it?
I forgot to heal, by the way.
So now it's not on cooldown.
Is it coming or what?
Yeah, this one is shit.
We gotta use this.
Just keep running.
We have, like, brief periods of respite here.
Someone's shooting lasers.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Nice, nice, nice.
It's going pretty well.
Man, it's actually shooting things.
It's shooting lasers.
This part is dangerous.
Keep going, keep going.
I was also considering actually changing my outfit.
Because if I'm only using this weapon right here,
maybe it's better to just change it.
Because, you know, more armor or something.
Oh, I'm taking damage from that.
Am I hitting something here or what?
Okay, okay, it's going pretty well.
It's going well, it's going well.
Believe in me!
Ah, the lasers.
Okay, it's coming, it's coming.
I think it's going faster and faster.
Getting more aggressive.
Oh no.
Keep going, keep going.
Don't get caught!
Oh my god!
Oh no.
Oh, I'm stuck!
Ah!
Oh, it killed me!
Oh wait, I'm not dead.
What's happening?
Okay, you don't insta-die.
God damn.
Holy crap.
Man, that was a good attempt though.
I feel like I'm getting more confident with this.
Like, I feel like I'm getting the fight down.
You know what I mean?
Okay.
That was good.
I want to go again.
It's just annoying to get back down there, man.
Oh, but wait, I'm also...
Oh, I'm using attempts on this because I don't have the...
I don't have a doll on me at all times.
Obviously.
I have one more left.
I'm not going to do it yet, man.
I'm going to wait until I have...
more buffs, I guess.
There's also some potions that I still want to make that I can't make yet.
First.
Yeah, I'm going to save it a bit.
Let's just save it a bit.
I don't want to use my last attempt here.
Especially because I don't feel 100% confident yet.
Oops.
What do I have?
Okay, empty inventory?
And then...
Let's just go digging somewhere.
Put this bag on, I guess.
Since I'm not going down there now.
This one I can also replace with that.
And this is a...
Actually, no.
Put this on.
These are nice to have, though.
Put them here.
I was noticing the hasty mana flower was cool.
Because it totally...
First of all, it reduces mana cost.
And it also automatically uses the mana potion.
So I don't have to think about that.
That's great.
Now click on this button here.
There we go.
And inside of here.
We put these two.
And the potions.
A bottle of water can stay here.
And then...
There.
Click on this.
And there.
Make another one.
And now we go exploring somewhere else.
And in fact,
because we're going somewhere else,
where we're probably going to be digging,
let me just bring my digging thing.
That is...
here, I believe?
Yep.
Replace...
that one.
And here's what I was thinking, by the way.
In that fight,
I wonder what the main source of damage I took was.
By the way, Sack is dead.
Bradley has arrived.
There's something demonic going on about the guide here, people.
This is not good.
I'm kind of afraid of him.
What's happening?
What's that?
Bewitched.
Oh, it's the witching thingy.
It will fight for you.
Look at all the banners I have.
Okay.
Do that.
Is that there?
And these.
Okay.
Fuck, I forgot what I wanted to do now.
I completely forgot.
Right.
The digging thing.
I have it.
Let's go.
I already got it.
So I want to go to ice now.
I want to go over here and dig down.
I want to see what's happening underneath the ice.
Let's check that out.
Top, top, top.
There we go.
So right now I'm immune to fire.
And now I'm not.
So I could just go like that, right?
Yep.
Also kind of an indicator of how fast you're going, that seems.
Or maybe not.
It's like a timer.
Keep going.
I guess I'm just going to do another straight down.
Is that too much?
No, it's not.
It's awesome.
Let's see what hides beneath the ice.
At least there's no water here.
Hold on, we've got a cave.
Let's see.
Keep going down.
Do I have my potion on me that will allow me to mine faster?
I do!
Awesome.
Oh!
Top, top, top, top, top.
So much better.
Just switch my finger here.
It's hard work holding the finger on the mouse, you know?
Wheeep.
Wait, have I been there?
Oh yeah, I have for sure.
Why did I put so many torches?
What is wrong with me?
That makes no sense.
I've been here too.
We're digging straight to hell.
Oh wait, I'm sort of stuck here.
These glow sticks have been with me all this time.
What is that?
What's that?
Oh.
These are the chests of this region.
Or the pots, I should say.
It's still ice here, by the way.
So this is jungle.
And it's like jungle all the way below as well.
So all of this is jungle, really.
So that means all of this is ice.
Well, until you reach a certain depth, right?
And...
You get to experience the demons.
Let me grab that.
Thank you.
Oh, it's so slippery here.
And the mining potion lasts 10 minutes as well.
That's really nice.
Okay, we've got a big cave.
Let's explore this a bit.
What's that?
Wait, is that a button?
Oh, it's a topos.
Oh, okay.
Whoa, look at that up there.
I see you.
I see you up there, sir.
I feel like my imps may not be very comfortable here
in this biome.
Too fucking bad.
Undead viking.
Snowflinks?
The fuck?
That's new.
Oh, they don't like the fire, I don't think.
Yo, this place is cool.
We even have a chest here.
Ice boomerang.
Ice mirror.
Oh.
Cool.
Flingsphere. It's so fluffy.
What's going on over there?
What the hell is that?
Spiked ice slime.
That's a trap there, by the way.
I see it.
Do I have the danger sense potion on me?
I'm afraid of this new biome.
Danger sense.
No, but I do have this.
I'll take it.
Okay.
Yeah, kill it.
Whoa.
Did it just break through the ice? Hold on.
Cool.
Oh, that's kind of neat.
Then we have this emerald.
Look at this place.
Oh, that was a trap.
We're okay though, we're okay.
I kind of forgot what I can use these life crystals for.
I mean, other than increasing my health, of course.
Where am I right now?
Okay.
I guess it's time to head back to...
to the hole.
I wonder if I can make an even longer...
hook...
or grapple thing.
Okay, here we are.
We need party lights.
Here we go.
Statue of a sword.
Ooh.
Don't want that.
Keep going down.
Hurtful trident.
Sandcastle bucket.
Danger sense, nice.
I will actually use that.
Oh my god, I keep breaking through.
Oh no.
Ah!
How do I stop breaking through?
Deposit all.
Delete things.
Slush block.
Oh wait, slush is...
I can use that, no?
That is usable.
In the thingy.
This is a material, so let's keep it.
Okay.
Danger sense.
Which one was it?
My god, I can't fucking find it.
Is it on me?
It is on me.
Okay.
So where did I go down here?
There we go.
Let's keep going.
In fact, I'm going to zoom out while I do this by the way.
Just so I can spot the treasure.
Like this for example.
A forceful snowball cannon.
Archery-type English stick.
Oh look at that.
Got a trigger there.
A detonator.
That scares me a little bit, but I want a present.
Okay, yeah.
Satisfying.
What's up with all the spiderwebs?
What?
Stumble into a spider cavern.
Oh no!
Really?
Where are the spiders?
I'm going to fuck them up.
Spiders!
Where you be?
I mean, I don't really see any.
What the heck?
This is where I came from, so straight down.
Okay, I'm just going to continue here.
Wait, did I see a chest?
What's that?
Oh, it's just cobwebs, never mind.
There's got to be something here, man.
What about over here?
What's lurking in the...
Oh, look at this!
Aha!
We've got a little...
Well, that's a trap.
I see the trap.
Oh, I see spiders now.
How do I trigger this trap without...
Oh, right, just remove it, right?
There we go.
Blinks fur?
Oh man, look at this place.
There are so many different biomes in this game.
Love this weapon so damn much.
I think it's my favorite now.
The magic missile is incredible.
So are these minions.
What is that right there?
That's a trap right there.
Give me that.
Is there anything down here?
Oh, there's a guy in here.
I don't know what his deal is though.
Hoplight.
Go right.
Ah, there's nothing in there though.
Let's do this.
Oh, wall creeper.
Disgusting.
Alright, there's nothing up here.
I'm gonna go back down here now.
Kill this fool.
Cool.
Keep going.
Oh, look at this.
What is that over there?
Whoa.
What is this place?
Oh, that's ice over there.
The ice that breaks.
Why am I so slow?
Oh, I'm chilled.
Chest.
A forceful breathing read.
Increases breath time and allows breathing in water.
Really?
How does that work?
Do I need that equipped or what?
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
Is that...?
Hold on.
It's slower.
Is it not slower?
I don't even have it equipped.
Wait, maybe it is not.
Hold on.
Look at that.
It actually works.
Look at it.
I bet if I go lower, yeah.
Amazing.
That's funny.
Okay, okay.
That's pretty cool.
It's neat detail there.
It's actually exactly what you expect.
I don't know why.
That's really funny to me.
Imagine finding that and going.
Oh, nice.
Now I'm going to use that.
It's kind of useless.
Shoe spikes.
My inventory is crap.
You there.
Let me quick stack you.
Sticky glow stick.
I want to delete this.
And that.
All of it.
Ah, the blink rule key actually.
Is this a material?
It's not even.
So get rid of it.
No, but wait.
It does actually work when it's my inventory.
Consume places.
Sand.
What do you mean?
I guess it needs to be on sand.
That would make sense to me.
Shark bait.
Someone's a shark prop.
Not really something I want.
Hold up to the sand slower.
Nurse Lisa.
Amazing.
Delete it.
Recall the gold.
All right.
Where to now?
I guess I just continue my downward trend.
Where's my downward trend?
Is it here?
There it is.
All the way down.
Thank you.
And there's a trap.
Here we go.
Oh, you know what?
Wait, why can't I...
Ah, we're in water.
It's time.
This is the perfect moment for this.
It's obsidian time.
So here's the question.
I will never be able to take damage from this
when I stand here and just spam, right?
Because whenever I destroy one,
it's actually gonna make obsidian below me.
So I can just do this.
Look at that.
Fantastic.
I need all of this obsidian.
So good.
Oh, wait.
Ooh.
I thought I was about to die.
I didn't pay attention to my breath.
Wait, I took damage.
So it's not 100% safe.
You gotta be a little careful, I guess.
There we go.
I'm taking all of this obsidian.
It is insanely useful.
Nice.
Okay.
At some point I'm gonna have all these
quick transport down to the bottom
of the world, across the entire world.
God, I'm mining slow.
Where's my thingy?
Oh, I do have it on me. Wow.
I felt like I was going way too slow.
Okay, well.
All right.
Wow.
Oh, look at that.
Something down there.
Be careful here.
Phew.
Close one.
What is that area?
Oh, it's just the standard lava.
It looks different, though.
More obsidian.
Oh, wait a minute.
No, I can't bomb this, right?
It doesn't work like that.
I need to mine this.
Oh, wait, it's using up the water to do it.
Of course.
So this is not actually something I can keep doing forever.
Yeah.
That's fine.
So this place looks interesting over here.
Why is the background different, right?
Huh.
Why does it look like that?
Let's blow some shit up.
Okay.
Oh, I see something on the left.
How's it going?
That's a healing potion.
This area again.
Is this the spider thing?
This stuff here on the walls is...
Spider, is it not?
Okay.
Wait, why does the map show me this?
Huh?
What's happening in there?
Let's see.
Ooh.
Oh, yeah, look at this.
Spider webs everywhere.
I also see a room here.
Dude, imagine mining the entire world.
You could literally remove every block.
Imagine doing that.
That would be crazy.
I mean, at some point there's nothing left.
Honestly, it's kind of weird knowing there's a limit.
There's an edge to the world.
Uh-oh.
Those are traps.
Come on.
Oh, no.
Fuck.
Fucking hell.
That was not ideal.
Nope.
Silt, let's use that right now.
Thank you.
But then, hold on, I also have the... was it slush?
I have no idea where it is.
Maybe it's in here.
Nice block.
Slush!
There it is.
Cobwebs.
And then...
Not to have like a buff like this on at any time.
Just have it on, you know?
No reason not to.
Oh, I'm gonna use this.
Hey.
There you go.
This is what I want to ask the guy about.
Also, slush, let's try it.
Yay!
It was slush, silt, and one more.
I forgot the last...
What's happening there?
Sir, why are you down here?
Bradley.
You guys are coming and going all the time.
A diamond!
I get the feeling diamond is really good for a diamond hook.
Yo!
I kind of want that.
I need ten diamonds though.
Shit.
No, I don't have that.
Actually, do I? Hold on. I have a gem chest.
No, I don't.
But you know what? Let me actually take all these.
Let me actually remind myself what these even do.
Bradley.
I have some questions. First obsidian.
What can I do with this again?
Oh!
Wait!
Wait a minute.
For defense.
Okay, this is not that great defense wise.
Oh, it's actually kind of the...
Dude, this suit is actually insane for...
the magic missile that I have.
I could do summon...
damage.
And I wonder what the set bonus is for this.
Oh, I need silk. How the fuck do I get that?
Wait, silk. Can I maybe use a loom?
Oh, wait a minute.
I need to know what to put in the loom.
Silk.
Cobweb?
Wait a minute.
That's how you extract silk, right?
Oh, fuck yeah, dude!
Loom!
Dude, this is such a victory for me right now. Holy shit!
Yeah!
Wait a minute, I have more.
Oh my god.
Wait.
Increases yo-yo range.
Sure, it's a material. Let's also...
Wait, plus 20 mana.
Dude.
Okay.
Silk.
Make a lot of silk.
And then...
Tell me about the silk.
No, click on new crafting.
Where's myself there?
What can I make?
Oh!
Maximum... wait, hold on!
Does this... oh wait, this is the same. Never mind.
I wonder if it stacks.
Dude, I can go full summon mode.
Obsidian.
This is the one.
But let me just take a look real quick.
Anything with stats?
Naughty present?
I don't know about that.
Incredibly old.
Well, obviously I'm gonna make this, I think.
Oh, wait, shadow scale? What the fuck is that?
I don't have that!
No!
No.
Okay, Dylan, what about this?
Oh.
Yo-yo glove. Hold on, there's more.
Purple... wait, I have a counterweight.
What is this even?
Master yo-yo skills.
Aha!
I don't have a yo-yo glove.
I don't have that.
This one I don't really want to do.
Tell me again about... is there anything? Hold on. Obsidian.
What else could I make with this?
This one?
What the fuck are fireblocks?
I guess I'll make some of these.
Fireblossom waterleaf. Yeah.
That's so needed.
Just a half.
Fireblossom. Oh, I can make a shit ton of these, boy.
Oh, and I also need... water?
There.
Now.
Yes.
Beautiful.
Tell me about these gems.
Hey, this is actually sick.
Hold on, sapphire?
Forty and nine.
Okay, so this is worse.
Oh, this is how I'm going to determine what is the best emerald?
Sixty!
Dude.
But look at the defense, man. It's very low.
It's very glass canony, isn't it?
Topos?
Forty.
Amber.
Sixty, but 13. Wait, 13.
Ruby must be good.
It's the same.
Wait, what was diamond again?
Eighty! Ho, ho, ho! Yeah.
Yeah, I don't have a lot of diamonds though.
I have one.
Diamond is definitely the best.
But you know what?
Can I not make a Topaz boot or something?
Or a headpiece?
Something like that?
Wait, I can make these?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on.
Hold on now.
Oh, this would suggest I should make a hook out of the best material of this.
Right now I have...
Whoops.
What do I have?
No, stop.
How do I see my...
Sapphire.
Wait a minute, Sapphire.
Which one was that?
This one. This is bad!
Let's make a...
Amber hook.
Wait, I need an animal.
Oh, look, it's actually ordered here.
This is probably the worst.
This is the best.
Amber.
So let's test.
So there.
Oh, definitely better!
Wait, how much better?
Okay, okay, nice, nice!
Very nice.
Let me sell some stuff.
That's gonna help me.
You take those.
And...
also have...
I don't even know, man.
Oh, the flinks fur. Let me try.
What about this?
What could I make?
Someone's a snow flinks to fight for you.
Flinks fur coat.
Dear thing.
Someone's...
Demonite or...
Wait, demonite?
I don't have that, do I?
Do I have that?
Doesn't ring a bell?
No.
I don't have that, man.
How come I don't have that?
Wouldn't I have gotten that down there from the demons?
Sandcastle pockets?
No clue what's that up, what that's all about.
Let's put it in here, I guess, for now.
This one I can sell.
The ice mirror.
It's a material.
I should try that with him.
Also, let me quickly press there.
Amber.
Wait, gems.
Which one is gems?
Gems.
Put them all back.
I kind of want to craft the chest so I can have one more summon.
But I forgot which one it was.
Dang it.
Which one was it?
You there?
Buy this for me.
Not Dylan.
Bradley is your name now.
I'm going to call you Brad.
What can I make with this?
What?
The PDA?
I want to make a PDA, dude.
Wait, why does it say cell phone right there?
Oh, it's because there's only one thing.
I understand.
Ruby.
There.
In.
Cobwebs can go back.
Still can also go in here.
This one is up here.
Fire Blossom.
Obsidian.
Okay.
Which one allowed me to make the one summon extra?
It was not this, was it?
It was.
Oh, but I can't make it because of shadow skill, right?
But there was another one with a gem, I believe.
So now, of course, I put all my gems away.
Great.
Let me just try these real quick.
Which one was it?
No, this is just reduced mana cost and stuff like that.
Ah, crap.
It was the Flingsphere, I believe.
But I couldn't make that either, right?
Reasons?
I don't even know where I put it.
No, don't rename sword flings.
I'm terrible at this, dude.
Must have been in here.
Bro, that thing is lost to me now.
That thing has gone off the face of the earth.
No idea where I put it.
God damn it.
Incredible.
Oh, up here maybe.
No.
Dude, man.
Where did I put it?
I can't fucking find my way around this inventory, dude.
Once you lose something, it's gone.
It's just so hard to find.
It's unreal.
Oh my god, what?
I have 16 magic power potions there.
What the heck?
Yo.
That thing is gone.
Alright, whatever.
Didn't want to make it anyway.
Put this in here.
The ore.
There.
Gems.
Here.
And then I want to go back immediately.
Let's go.
No dilly dallying.
I want to go...
Man.
This place.
Did I miss something here?
What is this?
There's something interesting there.
You know what, let's go back to the jungle.
Because this right here is a mystery that I would like to get to the bottom of.
I also want to see what's below the ocean if I dig over here.
Think about that for a second.
Yeah.
I kind of want to build another base somewhere over here.
I wonder if there's a way to change my respawn location.
Let's think about this.
How do I do that?
There's got to be a way to do that.
Or maybe not, actually.
The world is not that big, I guess.
The underworld is made of a material called hillstone.
Yeah.
Keeper of the...
Oh my god, he actually told me this last time.
Look!
Interesting that you would know this, huh?
The old ones army, yeah, yeah.
You can remove people from the...
Obsidian.
Some say there are giant beehives buried on the ground in the jungle.
I could do with some honey myself.
Speaking of that...
The honey.
I have no idea how to get that.
So let's try and find a beehive.
Put that in there.
Bottled water can go up here real quick.
You know what? No.
We're doing that.
Oh no!
What a terrible teleport!
Again.
Alright, fine.
I was hoping we'd get somewhere new.
In fact, I need to check what it takes to craft one of those teleportation potions.
I kind of want to make 2,000 of them.
And I do mean 2,000.
Two with three zeros.
Hello!
Wait, have I been?
No, I have not been here.
Oh my god!
Ha ha ha!
I don't know where I'm going right now.
I'm just going, you know?
I'm taking... I'm going wherever the wind guides me.
Even though there's no wind down here.
Wherever my heart takes me.
God damn it, I forgot to bring my summons.
Where am I right now?
I'm below the, I believe, forest.
Actually, no.
Taking back...
I'm going to go to the jungle.
I need to get to the bottom of that whole temple there.
I want to get inside so bad.
Real bad.
It's been bugging me for ages.
Just clear the way ahead.
Spam the button.
Eat one of these.
Accelerate.
We're not there yet.
So one thing about this game.
The bosses are fucking hard.
Like...
It's really difficult.
But I guess the thing I could do.
So...
The wall of flesh.
I guess I could make a platform that is infinitely long.
You know?
But I feel like...
I feel like that's kind of cheap.
You know?
Like spending half an hour to build.
I don't know.
A million yard-long platform.
Just to kill the boss.
I feel like that's not intended, in a way.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm just lazy.
It's also plausible.
Oh wait, we're in the jungle.
Okay.
What was I doing here again?
How do I gain entrance to that place?
I don't know.
I kind of want to just go straight down again, but I've been doing that a lot today.
Maybe change it up a bit.
In fact, I'm just going to go down where I already did go down.
And then just keep going around.
Yeah.
Wait a minute, why does this look like that?
That looks like some kind of messed up version of a jungle.
I'm going there.
Totally going there.
Ultimate speed.
God, it's dark.
Just hold the torch, I guess.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, this is the meteor place.
I know what fire blocks are.
It's these.
Of course, man.
I completely forgot about them.
I understand.
Okay.
Finally, it's clicking here.
That makes actually a lot of sense.
That was really annoying last time having to dig through that.
It's going to be really easy next time.
Wait, another one?
What the heck?
Oh, wait, this was the messed up jungle.
Here it is.
Like, this place is messed up.
Like, what is going on here, you know?
Let's dig.
Man, I have something in my eye.
Oh, this is going to be annoying.
200th meteor head.
I wonder if there's a meteor boss.
Okay.
We need light.
We also need the party.
Party!
So, wait a minute.
I'm not really in a jungle anymore now.
Look at this.
What the fuck?
It's only a little...
part.
Oh, no!
I almost died there.
We're okay.
Imagine dying in such shallow water.
That would be embarrassing.
That would never happen to me.
Also, dammit, we died today.
Yeah, this was not a deathless dream.
That's sad.
It makes me sad.
I even have my thing on and it's still so slow.
Oh!
Oh, yeah!
Damn.
That caught me off guard.
Wait, what?
It looks...
Never mind.
It looked interesting on the minimap.
Like, I hit something very big.
But I didn't.
Oh!
What is this?
Yo!
The night sky is in the background.
Look at that.
What the hell?
Look at this.
This is nice.
Failing.
Oh no, I should have brought my...
...bug in it.
I'm sorry.
I'm descending, guys!
I can't control my character.
I'm going back up.
That was so weird!
I'm back now.
Oh my god.
What happens when I do this?
Oh!
It pushes me through!
A shimmer in the dark.
Oh my god!
That's so weird!
Weird!
What the hell, dude?
What the hell?
Okay, I'm going to go...
I kind of want to go back up where I was here, though.
What is happening here?
Oh my god.
Dude, there's something I want to try, actually.
Oh, but wait, I don't have it on me.
Wait, look at this background here, by the way.
There's gems everywhere!
Okay, hold on.
I'm going to go up here and I'm going to try something.
But I need to go back home first...
...to grab it.
Uh...
You know what? Use this.
Oh, but wait, I don't want to go all the way up to the...
I don't want to make a hole through all of it again.
Oh, shit.
What's happening?
Oh, I had my hand on the wrong part of the keyboard.
So I was like, I couldn't hit my keybinds.
That was so weird just now.
Okay, so I'm going up left a bit here.
I think I know what to do here, guys.
I think you know as well, don't you?
Okay, we're almost there.
Man, this is so weird.
What the...
Shimmer slime!
Oh, I'm going to kill it.
Hold on, we need light.
Did that slime just get turned?
Riley the traveling merchant.
That's actually perfect.
I'm going back real quick.
Get away.
Arcane depth meter.
Oh, nice, I guess.
Okay, so here's what I'm going to do.
I need to go back.
Wait, do I not have my...
Hold on, what do I have in here?
Potion of return.
I don't have the thing I need.
So check this out.
This is maybe a bad idea.
But I'm doing it anyway.
Oh, no, I thought for sure something was going to happen.
No!
Okay, well, how do I grab it without falling through the shit?
Hey.
Oh my God, it bounces off!
That's amazing.
I was trying to throw...
Oh wait, I can't just leave it there.
I need to pick it up.
Hold on.
Can you get away from me, please?
Grab it.
Okay, nice.
So I was trying to throw...
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, I'm suffering from a debuff.
I couldn't move.
I was trying to throw the guide in there to see if I could somehow cure him of his voodooism.
You know?
Like, what's going on with that area, you know?
So he's obviously...
Oh my God, I'm hit again with this.
Oh, that's so annoying!
Kill everything!
Undead miner.
Don't need mana.
Have I been here?
I think I've...
Been here.
Before.
I'm actually not sure.
So what the hell is this place, man?
What do I do with this?
What is the point?
Let me go across.
Oh, what is that?
Oh no, I didn't mean to do that.
I thought I could stand on those blocks.
Oh no.
Uh-oh.
Okay, so it puts you to the next...
Cave, I guess.
Also, what is this background?
It's nothing, okay.
There's actually more gems.
Oh, dude!
I kind of want to put this into lava.
You know?
See what it makes?
Magic obsidian, maybe.
Oh wait, I'm...
Confused.
Why am I confused half the time here?
There's no enemies.
That's so weird.
Let me bring this down.
Okay, take me.
Where am I going?
Oh, I'm falling.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Definitely want to click on that, though.
Plop!
That's interesting.
Are we in the jungle now?
No, we're not.
Just look very green to me.
We are in the jungle!
Jungle spores!
Oh!
Wait, we're back here now in this.
This biome is so weird.
And so interesting.
What's happening, dude?
I'm gonna dig up.
Uh-oh.
Nah, I missed it.
Why did it change here?
Okay, so it went away there, but now it's...
Is it just because I'm close to the...
to the water or what?
Oh, oh, oh!
Look at that at the bottom!
There's something going on there.
A special block!
What is that?
Oh, I don't want to drain this on the side.
I need to go up.
Uh, this way.
No, actually, I do want to go this way.
Okay, let's be careful here.
Put it on manual.
Okay, so this one.
Ethereum block!
Ho-ho-ho!
What is that?
Look, it makes Ethereum when it touches water!
So I wonder what it does when it touches lava!
This is very interesting.
Oh, no, don't drain it.
Don't drain it.
Put...
Stone here.
There we go.
Oh, is it draining?
Is it draining?
Oh, no!
Ah, crap!
Fuck!
I'm an idiot.
Damn it!
Man, okay.
I gotta exit here.
Otherwise, yeah.
Oh, man!
Things are happening, huh?
Very interesting stuff this time.
Discovering weird things...
in the deep.
And a wall of flesh...
that's chasing me...
in the underworld.
My god.
This game is nuts, man.
Okay!
Let me...
Yeah, let's just keep it here.
How's everybody doing?
Clear the chat, people!
Exactly!
No spoilers anymore.
Never any spoilers, unless I ask for it.
Well, you can spoil other things, of course, while I'm playing
and you're talking amongst each other.
Of course.
Yeah, yeah.
Dylan was carrying the stream too hard.
People were anxiously awaiting his death.
Oh, really?
Amazing.
Yeah.
Man, Dylan!
I went through a lot of guides...
doing this.
Oh, what is that?
Cooking.
Oliver carefully picking some of the most annoying moments to end the stream.
Ah!
It's not on purpose, I swear.
I tried to keep it around the three-hour mark, so...
Great time experimenting, huh?
Yes!
Indeed.
Having lots of fun with experimenting in this game.
No, it's over already!
I'm sorry, North Star.
When you think about the game so far, I love it.
Yeah, in 587.
It's really fun.
My favorite part is digging.
Even though it sounds a little boring to say, but I love digging tunnels
and just going left and right exploring everything.
Finding loot.
Gives me dopamine.
Oliver, the idea you got from doing a path fighting wall of flesh is a good one.
You think so?
I don't know, maybe.
But don't give me hints or anything.
Just in general.
Demon guides.
Hope you all have a day as beautiful as you are.
So...
Say we all.
Talona Rose.
You've been saying that ever since Minecraft.
I remember that.
Thank you.
I love a good dick, too.
Will there be a 3D version of this?
Oh, you mean of the game?
I don't know.
That could be kind of cool.
I guess Minecraft is the closest thing to it.
Oh, it's not a spoiler?
Oh, okay.
Y'all are awesome, indeed.
So have you found the shiny liquid?
Love it, sparkle.
Yeah, man, it's...
When I saw the stars in the background, I was like,
what the fuck is happening?
I was both scared and in awe.
At the same time.
The ooloon!
With 5 pounds.
Thank you, man.
I've been having tons of fun in your community
and the MC server.
I'm so glad to have found your channel,
some amazing people here.
You know, speaking of the MC server,
I kind of want to go in there again
and check it out at some point.
Because I know people are still playing on it
and doing amazing things.
Apparently there's a whole sub-community
in the MC channel.
I think that's so funny.
People are having great times making friends.
It's lovely to see.
Terraria 4D.
That would be in VR, I guess.
If you count time as a dimension as well.
What difficulty are you playing on?
I think it's called Expert, yeah.
Honestly, I kind of regret picking it.
Because the game is very difficult on Expert.
But the only reason I took it
is because it said there was a special loot to be had.
So I was like, I gotta do it.
Probably if it wouldn't have said that
I would have just picked the normal difficulty.
You think you'll be able to kill the wall of flesh next stream?
Maybe.
It's a skill issue, I guess.
So it depends on whether or not I will perform.
And I'm not an expert right now at this.
Oh my god, loot! We're gifted 5
memberships to people in the channel.
Thank you, man.
That's so generous of you.
Who are the ones who got it?
I'll see if I can see that.
Actually, I don't think there's a way for me to see it.
It's like, no, I can't see it.
People know who it is, I think.
Mikey the Great.
Playing this game blind is a good way to play,
although sometimes it hurts watching you play.
But mostly it's really unique and fun to watch.
I mean, that's how it is with all games, I think.
I mean, when I finish a game and I watch someone else play it,
I feel the same way.
It's just like, oh my god, he's not doing it the right way, you know?
But you gotta remember
that when you don't know anything about the game,
it's really hard to put yourself back
into the shoes of the time
when you didn't know anything about the game, right?
So some of these mistakes that I'm making,
I guess it's kind of natural.
Thanks so much, Ludwig.
You're a very welcome team.
We are a team.
We have such a great community on the Discord.
If anyone hasn't joined it yet, get in there.
It's fun. The green guy!
Don't worry, expert was the right choice.
Cool. That makes me feel good.
What does this mean?
Yes, but this one hurts physically.
I'm so sorry.
Take some painkillers next time.
Ibuprofen.
Pump your system full of it
before you venture into this stream.
Oliver, you should definitely try this game called Valheim.
I do want to try it, but when it's out of early access.
I played a couple hours with my friend,
some years ago, and it was amazing.
And we thought, holy shit, we got to wait until the full release.
Yeah, people have been playing this game for 12 years
and forget how it is to not know everything.
Yeah.
It's very hard to unlearn things you know about, right?
Once you know it, it's very hard to just instantly forget about it.
It's actually impossible.
I'm going to play Undertale at some point for sure.
Babel, Hexagon, 2x.
What a weirdly specific name, but I like it.
If you definitely try computers, these are fire?
I love computers, man.
I agree. Computers are fire.
Hell yeah.
The community manages to keep Terraria alive or Terraria.
Oh guys, is it Terraria or Terraria?
How do I say it correctly?
I'm really amazed at the players to keep the devs working on this game.
Yeah, this game is apparently...
apparently there's a big patch coming soon.
1.5. I heard about that.
Terraria.
I've heard both.
I like how you just say it's Terraria.
People say...
Okay, I'm going to say Terraria from now on.
Is that a reference to the library of Babel?
Which stores books in numbered hexagons?
I don't even know what that is.
Oh, you're talking to Babel, sorry.
Well, like a Terrarium and Terra for Earth.
They both mean Terra for Earth from the Greek.
That makes a lot of sense, panboy2k.
That's what I thought as well.
I went through the same...
conclusions during the stream, actually.
I've said Terraria since 2013.
I don't know if there is a correct pronunciation.
I guess both are right.
People saying both are good, so I think you're good.
Okay, man.
I need to eat.
Actually, I don't have any food, so I need to go to the store first.
Buy some food and then eat that food.
And I'm going to eat it while watching StarCraft.
Hell yeah, dude. StarCraft tournaments.
Is anyone in here fans of StarCraft?
StarCraft 2?
Does any of you watch StarCraft 2 in here?
Am I alone in this or...?
I'm actually just curious about this.
I feel like nobody does.
You're a huge fan.
Oh, Hedgehog!
Yeah, I remember when I was streaming StarCraft in the beginning here on the channel.
I remember we were talking.
Yep.
Silver Saber 62.
Nice.
Mainly for the lore and campaigns, but multiplayer is fun, too.
More of a Warcraft guy.
I... Rattle Shirt.
I've actually never played Warcraft 3 online, like against other people.
I've played a little bit of the campaign and I actually do want to complete it one day.
I'm never a fan of RTS. That's fine.
It's not for a lot of people.
It's a very niche thing.
Sacred Cat.
I like watching esports.
Any game doesn't matter what game.
When is the next stream, North Star?
I don't know.
Either tomorrow or Monday, I would say.
But I have a lot of stuff happening in my life right now.
And I'm kind of addicted to StarCraft as well, so I'm trying to balance everything.
You know?
Yep.
Okay.
Guys, I'm out of here.
Have a good night.
Enjoy your Saturday and thank you for the Gifted Sobs, Ludwig, and the Ovaloon.
I don't know how to pronounce your name correctly there, but thank you for the donations
and for watching and just hanging out and creating this awesome community.
See you guys around.
Adiós!